A Guide to the Herbert E. Harris II Papers
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
- Series III: Legislation Files
  - Subseries A: Legislative Information Files
    - HR 5829: Relief of Harry Spaulding, Jr. (Box Box 72)
    - HR 5991: To prohibit discrimination against elderly in renewal credit (Box Box 72)
    - HR 6166: The "Neighborhood Conservation Act" (Box Box 72)
    - HR 6168: To terminate Airlines Mutual Aid Agreement (Box Box 72)
    - HR 6214: Direct Sec. of Defense to operate commissary stores (Box Box 72)
    - HR 6227: Federal Employees right to representation (Box Box 72)
    - HR 6231 (5181): Education Amendment of 1974 regarding impact aid (Box Box 72)
    - HR 6232: Department heads to notify Congress on changes affecting employment (Box Box 72)
    - HR 6266: Protect petroleum product dealers from unfair practices (Box Box 72)
    - HR 6292 (21): The "Health Security Act of 1975" (Box Box 72)
    - HR 6300: Establish summer job program for youth on farms, ranch (Box Box 72)
    - HR 6360 (3428): Metro Transit authority for Transit Police Force (Box Box 72)
    - HR 6360: Federal-Local Cost Sharing for METRO Construction (Box Box 72)
    - HR 6383: Increased employment opportunity for nonstandard hours (Box Box 72)
    - HR 6431: Prohibiting restrictive trade practices (Box Box 72)
    - HR 6624: Wilderness in Shenandoah National Park - 6892 (Box Box 72)
    - HR 6712: A bill to correct abuses in IRS re privacy on taxation (Box Box 72)
    - HR 6883: Enlarge Sequoia National Park (Box Box 72)
    - HR 7137: To improve Nation's Energy Resources (Box Box 72)
    - HR 7215: Amend Omnibus Crime bill for Officer's Bill of Rights (Box Box 72)
    - HR 7222: Increase Government Contribution to Employees Group Life Insurance (Box Box 72)
    - HR 7243: Amend Housing Act re: Condominium insurance (Box Box 72)
    - HR 7244: Amend Internal Revenue Code to exempt Co-ops & Condominiums (Box Box 72)
    - HR 7482: Right of Privacy on Financial Information (Box Box 72)
    - HR 7529: Regulate commerce & protect petroleum dealers (7530) (Box Box 72)
    - HR 7531: June 3, 1975 Retirement Annuities Federal Personnel (pre 7/18) (Box Box 72)
    - HR 7532: June 3, 1975 Amend Internal Revenue Code Provide Credit on House Purchase (Box Box 72)
    - HR 7606: Terminating Mine Safety Board Review (Box Box 72)
    - HR 7000; HR 7658: Social Security Medicare higher nursing costs (Box Box 72)
    - HR 7733: Expand Indiana Dunes Park (Box Box 72)
    - HR 7766: Restore Champus Military Benefits (Box Box 72)
    - HR 7931: Voluntary Withholding State & Washington, D.C. Income Tax (Box Box 72)
    - HR 7976: Annual Leave Restored on Unjustified Personnel Actions (Box Box 72)
    - HR 7977: Either House Disapprove certain Executive Agency Rules (Box Box 72)
    - HR 7989: Establish Valley Forge National Park in Pennsylvania (Box Box 72)
    - HR 8028: Prohibit discriminatory employment practices against handicapped (Box Box 72)
    - HR 8212: Extend the Emergency Medical Services Act of 1972 (Box Box 72)
    - HR 8262: Amend National Wildlife Refuge Systems Administration (Box Box 72)
    - HR 8332: Compensate Local Governments for tax immunity Federal Lands (Box Box 72)
    - HR 8495: Establish Research & Development for Energy Conserving Industrial Technologies (Box Box 72)
    - HR 8550: Amend annuities on remarriage (Box Box 72)
    - HR 8617: Revise Hatch Act - restore certain rights (Box Box 72)
    - HR 8719: Amend METRO compact to provide security (protection) (Box Box 72)
    - HR 8763: Amend authority National Banks in state & local securities (Box Box 72)
    - HR 8847: Amend Social Security Act for Right of Reconsideration on benefit claims (Box Box 72)
    - HR 8943: Prohibit Oil Company Control of Alternate Energy Sources (Box Box 72)
    - HR 9018: Washington, D.C. Government to enter into compacts with states (Box Box 72)
    - HR 9018: Authorize Washington, D.C. to enter compacts with State(s) (Box Box 73)
    - HR 9021: Legislative Organization Act - provide seminars to Freshmen Congress (Box Box 73)
    - HR 9025: Establish Federal Corporate Chartering Commission (Box Box 73)
    - HR 9059: Amend Social Security Act to expedite ADC to payments to states (Box Box 73)
    - HR 9100: Congressional Public Financing Act of 1975 (Box Box 73)
    - HR 9104: Public financing of congressional election campaigns (Box Box 73)
    - HR 9122 (10241): To establish a Department of Education (Box Box 73)
    - HR 9244: Service-connected Disability Care for Veterans (Box Box 73)
    - HR 9287: Authorize a two-cent Bicentennial Coin (Box Box 73)
    - HR 9330: Amend titles XX Social Security Act - requires no "means test" for those 60 or over (Box Box 73)
    - HR 9380: Amend National Flood Insurance Act - losses/ landslides (Box Box 73)
    - HR 9392: Fair Marketing of Petroleum Products Act (Box Box 73)
    - HR 9440: Revise date for Executive employee pay comparability adjustments to same date (Box Box 73)
    - HR 9451: Amend Civil Rights Act of 1968 - marital status (Box Box 73)
    - HR 9507: Establish conservation corps in the Agriculture & Interior Departments (Box Box 73)
    - HR 9510: Regulate Commerce to Assure Supply of Natural Gas (Box Box 73)
    - HR 9580: Amend Social Security Act/ expedite replacement lost checks (Box Box 73)
    - HR 9587: Amend Social Security Act/ expedite Federal payments to states AFDC, etc. (Box Box 73)
    - HR 9601: Crediting Females sworn in Telephone Operating Units (Box Box 73)
    - HR 9684: Income Credit for Higher Education (Box Box 73)
    - HR 9905: Pay Plans for Federal Employees (Box Box 73)
    - HR 9961: To amend the National Housing Act (Box Box 73)
    - HR 10414: Bill for the Relief of George Chiplock (Box Box 73)
    - HR 11140: Veteran's National Cemetery, (3 folders) (Box Box 73)
    - HR 9608: Virgin Islands Constitutions (Box Box 73)
    - HR 9634: Co-sponsored emergency medical service (Box Box 73)
    - HR 9674: Amend Fair Packaging & Labeling Act - aerosol disclose information re propellents (Box Box 73)
    - HR 9796: Limit cost of living Federal Executive salaries to 5% (Box Box 73)
    - HR 9994: Amend title 5, U.S. Code court leave to Federal employees (Box Box 73)
    - HR 10607: Energy and Tax Reform (Box Box 73)
    - HR 10135: Amend Sec. 552A - U.S. Code disclose information re casework (Box Box 73)
    - HR 10217: Federal Payment to Washington, D.C. (Box Box 73)
    - HR 10440: Study Federal payment to Washington, D.C. (Box Box 73)
    - HR 10514: Amend Truth in Lending post current interest rates for loans (Box Box 73)
    - HR 10859: Reform Electric Utility Rate Regulation (Box Box 73)
    - HR 10678: Reinstate civil service survivor annuities widows/ widowers (Box Box 73)
    - HR 10872: Correct Inequities in certain Franchise Practices (Box Box 73)
    - HR 10960: Safeguard taxpayer rights Restrict inspection of Federal Tax Returns (Box Box 73)
    - HR 11009: Independent Audit Financial condition of Washington, D.C. (Box Box 73)
    - HR 11074: Health Benefits (Box Box 73)
    - HR 11108: The Payment of Interests by Federal Agencies (Box Box 74)
    - HR 11116: Library of Congress James Madison Building (Box Box 74)
    - HR 11213: Rent assistance for the unemployed (Box Box 74)
    - HR 11424: Establish a Department of Education (Box Box 74)
    - HR 11438: Court leave for federal employees (Box Box 74)
    - HR 11692: Prohibit Supersonic Aircraft in U.S. (Box Box 74)
    - HR 11822: Remove time limitations on veterans education programs (Box Box 74)
    - HR 11944: Remove ceiling on General Schedule pay rates (Box Box 74)
    - HR 13588: Civil Service Commission / Independent Regulatory Commissions (Box Box 74)
    - HR 14061: To increase the membership of the Civil Service Commission (Box Box 74)
    - HR 14162: National Commission on Alternatives to Busing (Box Box 74)
    - HR 14358: Deny tax benefits to bribers of foreign government agents (Box Box 74)
    - HR 14607: Tax Reduction (Box Box 74)
    - HR 11875: Establish Potomac National River (Box Box 74)
    - HR 11971: Establish series of six regional primaries (Box Box 74)
    - HR 12090: Pipelines; Petroleum (Box Box 74)
    - HR 12087: To prohibit SST from landing at Dulles or National (Box Box 74)
    - HR 12123: To provide for public financing of Congressional election (Box Box 74)
    - HR 12127: To amend PL 874, Eighty-first congress (Box Box 74)
    - HR 12136: To establish the Federal Election Commission (Box Box 74)
    - HR 12170: To prohibit SST's that do not meet noise requirements (Box Box 74)
    - HR 12180: To reform residential electric utility rates (Box Box 74)
    - HR 12561: Recycling organic waste materials (Box Box 74)
    - HR 12635: To postpone all pay raises for Congressmen until the next Congress (Box Box 74)
    - HR 12661: A program for preservation of historic properties (Box Box 74)
    - HR 12684: To amend the rules of evidence in rape cases (Box Box 74)
    - HR 12747: A commission on food production, processing, marketing... (Box Box 74)
    - HR 12761: Electric utility reform bill (Box Box 74)
    - HR 12946: A commission to study the federal payment to Washington, D.C. (Box Box 74)
    - HR 13072: Extension of emergency unemployment program (Box Box 74)
    - HR 13108: To extend specially adapted housing for disabled veterans (Box Box 74)
    - HR 13250: To adjust the salary of the U.S. Park Police (Box Box 74)
    - HR 13372: Preservation of the New River (Box Box 74)
    - HR 13521: Federal Employee Health Benefits (Box Box 74)
    - HR 13536: Sugar content disclosure on food products (Box Box 74)
    - HR 13588: Co-sponsored increased Civil Service Commission from 3 to 5 (Box Box 74)
    - HR 13620: Social Security protection for widows & widowers (Box Box 74)
    - HR 13783: Noise emission controls on aircraft (Box Box 74)
    - HR 13812: Government payment of interest on overdue contracts (Box Box 74)
    - HR 13849: Commemorative Stamp of Martin Luther King, Jr. (Box Box 74)
    - HR 13917: Inclusion of services of nurses in Medicare (Box Box 74)
    - HR 13934: Restate the charter of George Washington University (Box Box 74)
    - HR 14322: Washington, D.C. Police & Firemen's Salary (Box Box 74)
    - HR 14398: Reform Electric Utility Rate (Box Box 74)
    - HR 14624: Cosponsored to expand assistance to minority Small Business Act (Box Box 74)
    - HR 14631: Cosponsored Internal Revenue Code current table (Box Box 74)
    - HR 14666: Cosponsored Privacy of rape victims (Box Box 74)
    - HR 14696: Cosponsored Energy Policy & Conservation Act (Box Box 74)
    - HR 14842: Cosponsored for abolition of certain Federal agencies (Box Box 74)
    - HR 15046: Amend B of Title XI Social Security Act re nurses (Box Box 74)
    - HR 15065: Tax credit $250 Health Insurance Expenditures (Box Box 74)
    - HR 15181: Amend Title II Social Security Act - cost of living semiannual basis (Box Box 74)
    - HR 15184: Indemnity participants swine flu inoculation (Box Box 74)
    - HR 15188: Salary M. of C. not be effective until next Congress (Box Box 74)
    - HR 15276: Amend Washington, D.C. Police/ Firemen's salary Act '58 Park Police/ Fed/ Pay (Box Box 74)
    - HR 15430 (14638): Disposal of sludge (Box Box 74)
    - HR 15434: Equitable rate for water in Washington, D.C. - to encourage water conservation (Box Box 74)
    - HR 15501: Restate the Charter of George Washington University (Box Box 74)
    - HR 15626: Amend Federal Power Act - consider proposed electric utility rate increase (Box Box 74)
    - HR 15733: Amend Public Health Services Act - Medical practices, training, & study (Box Box 74)
    - HR 15734: Cosponsor Amend the Public Health Service Act (Box Box 74)
    - HR 15784: Dealing with the abuse of diplomatic immunity (Box Box 74)
    - HR 83: Sponsored - Washington, D.C. Water Conservation (Box Box 75)
    - HR 664, 3745, 4713, 4793, 7212: Contract Disputes Act - 1977 (Box Box 75)
    - HR 2558: Sponsored - 1/26/77 Relief of Dr. John Alexis L.S. Tam (Box Box 75)
    - HR 2761: Sponsored - 1/31/77 Relief of Su-Hwan Choe (Box Box 75)
    - HR 2991: Sponsored - 1/31/77 Ethics Bill for Members of Congress (Box Box 75)
    - HR 12451: Sponsored - 5/1/78 Disregard certain changes in tax laws in treatment of individuals as employees (Box Box 75)
    - HR 683: Cosponsored - Amend 1/4/77 Clayton Act - Energy-producing Industries (Box Box 75)
    - HR 779: Cosponsored - 1/4/77 Review Federal Agencies etc. (Box Box 75)
    - HR 929: Cosponsored - 1/11/77 Prohibit Control/ Energy Sources (Box Box 75)
    - HR 988: Cosponsored - 1/4/77 Effect judicial proceedings re custody of children (Box Box 75)
    - HR 1656: Cosponsored - 1/11/77 Fair Packaging/ Labeling Act (Box Box 75)
    - HR 1734: Cosponsored - 1/11/77 Potomac River construction of weir (Box Box 75)
    - HR 1772: Cosponsored - 1/12/77 Enlarge Sequoia National Park in California (Box Box 75)
    - HR 2087: Cosponsored - 1/19/77 Relieve taxpayers Sick Pay/ tax reform (Box Box 75)
    - HR 2184: Cosponsored - 1/19/77 Fair Packaging/ Labeling Act (Box Box 75)
    - HR 2186: Cosponsored - 1/19/77 Durable products labeled (Box Box 75)
    - HR 2382: Cosponsored - 1/26/77 Review of Federal Agencies (Box Box 75)
    - HR 2396: Cosponsored - 1/26/77 Restore Federal & Postal Service employee rights to participate in the politics (Box Box 75)
    - HR 2532: Cosponsored - 1/26/77 Women/ minorities mortgage credit (Box Box 75)
    - HR 2700: Cosponsored - 2/1/77 Restate charter George Washington University (Box Box 75)
    - HR 2702: Cosponsored - 2/1/77 Eliminate some diplomatic immunity (Box Box 75)
    - HR 2704: Cosponsored - 2/1/77 Exclusion/ disability retirement (Box Box 75)
    - HR 2722: Cosponsored - 4/6/77 Collective bargaining/ postal employees (Box Box 75)
    - HR 2777: National Consumer Cooperative Bank Act (Box Box 75)
    - HR 2973: Cosponsored - 1/31/77 Martin Luther King Jr. holiday (Box Box 75)
    - HR 3004: Cosponsored - 2/2/77 Meals-on-wheels national elderly (Box Box 75)
    - HR 3098: Cosponsored - 2/3/77 Amend Bankruptcy Act (Box Box 75)
    - HR 3116: Cosponsored - 2/3/77 Amend Arms Export Control Act (Box Box 75)
    - HR 3140: Cosponsored - 2/7/77 requirements to notify Congress before the closure of a military installation (Box Box 75)
    - HR 3161: Sponsored - Firefighters Statements, Hearings, Bills, Summary, Reports (Box Box 75)
    - HR 3161: Sponsored - Firefighters Correspondence, petitions, questions (Box Box 75)
    - HR 3167: Cosponsored - 2/7/77 Nurses/ Social Security/ peer review (Box Box 75)
    - HR 3242: Cosponsored - 2/8/77 Retire disability exclusion (Box Box 75)
    - HR 3291: Cosponsored - 2/8/77 Amend Federal Food, Drug, & Cosmetic Act to disclose sugar content (Box Box 75)
    - HR 3551: Cosponsored - 2/16/77 Earthquake Hazards Reduction Act (Box Box 75)
    - HR 3745: Sponsored - Contract Disputes - drafts (Box Box 75)
    - Statements (contract disputes), n.d. (Box Box 76)
    - HR 3873: Cosponsored - 2/23/77 Protect Franchised Retail Motor Fuel (Box Box 76)
    - HR 4055: Cosponsored - 2/24/77 Tanker safety - Ports & waterways (Box Box 76)
    - HR 4011: Cosponsored - 2/24/77 National Health Insurance (Box Box 76)
    - HR 4118: Cosponsored - 2/28/77 Federal Agencies expenditures (Box Box 76)
    - HR 4176: Cosponsored - 3/1/77 Federal State & Local electric rates rules (Box Box 76)
    - HR 4327: Cosponsored - 3/2/77 Cost-of-living Social Security increase (Box Box 76)
    - HR 4333: Cosponsored - 3/2/77 Transfer historic sites to Colonial National Historical Park (Box Box 76)
    - HR 4368: Cosponsored - 3/2/77 Amend Social Security Act to include eligible drugs (Box Box 76)
    - HR 4463: Cosponsored - 3/3/77 Study National Park east of San Francisco, California (Box Box 76)
    - HR 4728: Cosponsored - 3/9/77 Privacy of rape victims (Box Box 76)
    - HR 5054: Sponsored - 3/15/77 Apportionment (Box Box 76)
    - HR 5058: Cosponsored - 3/15/77 Prohibits sex discrimination (Box Box 76)
    - HR 5159: Cosponsored - 3/16/77 Limit public financing for congressional general elections (Box Box 76)
    - HR 5301: Cosponsored - 3/22/77 Research auto propulsion systems (Box Box 76)
    - HR 5330: Sponsored - 3/22/77 Civil Service grade retention (Box Box 76)
    - HR 5487: Cosponsored - 3/23/77 Downgrading Federal employees (Box Box 76)
    - HR 5544: Cosponsored - 3/23/77 Executive Supergrade Bill (Box Box 76)
    - HR 5571: Cosponsored - 3/24/77 Lenders post current interest rates (Box Box 76)
    - HR 5628: Cosponsored - 3/28/77 Retirement/ annuity/ survivor 1- year (Box Box 76)
    - HR 5788: Cosponsored - 3/30/77 Solar energy devices GSA to procure (Box Box 76)
    - HR 5849: Cosponsored - 3/31/77 To audit certain agency expenditures (Box Box 76)
    - HR 5872: Cosponsored - 3/31/77 Industrial technology & energy conservation (Box Box 76)
    - HR 5908: Cosponsored - 3/31/77 Solar energy incentives (Box Box 76)
    - HR 5913: Cosponsored - 3/31/77 Solar energy research, development (Box Box 77)
    - HR 5920: Cosponsored - 3/31/77 Solar energy promotion (Box Box 77)
    - HR 5957: Cosponsored - 4/4/77 Franchise Practices Reform Act (Box Box 77)
    - HR 6009: Cosponsored - 4/5/77 Electric energy rate making (Box Box 77)
    - HR 6114: Cosponsored - 4/6/77 Solar energy/ family farms (Box Box 77)
    - HR 6115: Cosponsored - 4/6/77 Solar energy/ housing programs (Box Box 77)
    - HR 6116: Cosponsored - 4/6/77 Solar energy/ vets - heating, cooling systems (Box Box 77)
    - HR 6141: Cosponsored - 4/6/77 Prohibit discrimination re marital status (Box Box 77)
    - HR 6210: Cosponsored - 4/6/77 Franchise practices, competition (Box Box 77)
    - HR 6228: Cosponsored - 4/6/77 Building of weir/ before study (Box Box 77)
    - HR 6231: Cosponsored - 4/6/77 Lowell National Cultural Park/ Mass. (Box Box 77)
    - HR 6326: Sponsored - 4/19/77 White House Personnel/ Political (Box Box 77)
    - HR 6488: Sponsored - 4/21/77 Foreign adopted children (Box Box 77)
    - HR 6412: Cosponsored - 4/20/77 Japanese-Americans civil service retirement (Box Box 77)
    - HR 6509: Cosponsored - 4/21/77 OSHA for Congress & Federal Agencies (Box Box 77)
    - HR 6536: Cosponsored - 4/21/77 Washington, D.C. retirement for Police, Firemen, Teachers (Box Box 77)
    - HR 6540: Cosponsored - 4/21/77 Consumers - cooperatives (Box Box 77)
    - HR 6666: Cosponsored - 4/27/77 Legal Services Corporation Amendments Act appropriations (Box Box 77)
    - HR 6683: Cosponsored - 4/27/77 Hazards of earthquakes (Box Box 77)
    - HR 6723: Cosponsored - 4/28/77 Civilian Conservation Corps for Agriculture and Interior (Box Box 77)
    - HR 6748: Sponsored - 4/28/77 Tax Credit for college costs (Box Box 77)
    - HR 7052: Cosponsored - 5/10/77 Ex-offenders right to vote in Federal Elections (Box Box 77)
    - HR 7084: Cosponsored - 5/11/77 Recognize Women's Air Forces Service Pilots in World War II (Box Box 77)
    - HR 7231: Cosponsored - 5/17/77 Boundary Waters Canoe Area (Box Box 77)
    - HR 7338: Sponsored - 5/23/77 Social Security not reduced-cost-of-living (Box Box 77)
    - Tuition Tax Credit Resource Information, n.d. (Box Box 77)
    - HR 7083: Sponsored - 5/10/77 Relief of Ho Sun Pak (Box Box 77)
    - HR 7406: Cosponsored - 5/24/77 Protect citizens' privacy (Box Box 77)
    - HR 7467: Cosponsored - 5/26/77 Senate House phone for deaf (Box Box 77)
    - HR 7483: Cosponsored - 5/18/77 Social Security/ prompt payment (Box Box 77)
    - HR 7582: Cosponsored - 6/2/77 CHAMPUS (Box Box 77)
    - HR 7600: Cosponsored - 6/3/77 Federal Employee/ right to hearings etc. (Box Box 77)
    - HR 7769: Cosponsored - 6/14/77 Permanent residence for refugees - Vietnam, Laos, etc (Box Box 77)
    - HR 7769: Cosponsored - Status of Indochinese refugees to Permanent residence (Box Box 77)
    - HR 7782: Cosponsored - 6/14/77 Control/ Federal lands - energy (Box Box 77)
    - HR 7784: Cosponsored - 6/14/77 Trade/ transport of petroleum (Box Box 77)
    - HR 8147: Sponsored - To improve basic workweek of Firefighting personnel (see HR 3161) (Box Box 77)
    - HR 8173: Cosponsored - Limit motor vehicles used by government agencies (Box Box 77)
    - HR 8230: Sponsored - To amend Omnibus Crime Control & Safe Streets Act of 1968 (Box Box 77)
    - HR 8332: Sponsored - To limit Number of executive level positions (Box Box 77)
    - HR 8342: Cosponsored - To provide for withholding taxes for Federal employees (Box Box 77)
    - HR 8462: Sponsored - To limit number of executive level positions (see HR 8332) (Box Box 77)
    - HR 8494: Cosponsored - To regulate lobbying and related activities (Box Box 77)
    - HR 8506: no description (Box Box 77)
    - HR 8559: Sponsored - To amend Internal Revenue Code to eliminate tax credit paid to foreign countries (Box Box 77)
    - HR 8771: Cosponsored - Court decree of Federal retirement annuity to spouse (Box Box 77)
    - HR 8796: Cosponsored - To allow contributions to arts from income tax (Box Box 77)
    - HR 8798: Cosponsored - To permit awards of attorney fees in Federal agency proceedings (Box Box 77)
    - HR 8966: Cosponsored - Research for Sludge Disposal (Box Box 77)
    - HR 8973: Cosponsor - Amend Interstate Commerce Act for Motor Carrier Operation (Box Box 77)
    - HR 9146: Cosponsor - To provide Congress review of changes in Postal Services (Box Box 77)
    - HR 9199: Cosponsor - To establish loan program for drought impacted districts (Box Box 77)
    - HR 9454: Cosponsor - To authorize Sec. of Transportation to make grants for bikeways (Box Box 77)
    - HR 9471: Cosponsor - To provide Civil Service Retirement credit to Japanese in Internment Camps during World War II (Box Box 77)
    - HR 9490: Cosponsored - Eliminate income limitation on the credit of elderly (Box Box 78)
    - HR 9559: Sponsored - To amend Omnibus Crime Control Act and Safe Streets Act (Box Box 78)
    - HR 9560: Sponsored - To admit more than two foreign adopted children (Box Box 78)
    - HR 9590: Sponsored - Federal employee health benefits (Box Box 78)
    - HR 9718 (9697): Cosponsored - To establish Office of Consumer Representation (Box Box 78)
    - HR 9730: Cosponsored - To include outpatient rehabilitation in Medicare (Box Box 78)
    - HR 10118: Cosponsored - Commission to study Federal pay to Washington, D.C. (Box Box 78)
    - HR 10126: P.L. 95-437 Part-time career opportunities (Box Box 78)
    - HR 10145: Cosponsored - Authority of national banks to underwrite securities by state and local governments (Box Box 78)
    - HR 10175: Cosponsored - To permit teachers to change employment across state lines (Box Box 78)
    - HR 10271: Cosponsored - To amend FEC Act for political committee contributions (Box Box 78)
    - HR 10302: Cosponsored - To provide for psychologists services under Supplementary Medical Insurance Benefits (Box Box 78)
    - HR 10465: Sponsored - 1/19/78 Social Security Offset Bill (Box Box 78)
    - HR 10986: Cosponsored - Broadcasting of certain professional sports clubs' games (Box Box 78)
    - HR 11002: Sponsored - 2/20/78 Contract Disputes (Box Box 78)
    - HR 11003: Sponsored - 2/20/78 White House Staffing Authority (Box Box 78)
    - HR 11008: Cosponsored - To authorize Smithsonian Institute to acquire Museum of African Art (Box Box 78)
    - HR 11058: Cosponsored - To improve Congress oversight of Federal programs by Review of Authority (Box Box 78)
    - HR 11095: Cosponsored - To exclude from admission & deport from U.S. aliens who persecuted others for their religion, race, or origin (Box Box 78)
    - HR 11165: Sponsored - 2/27/78 Merit Employment (Box Box 78)
    - HR 11307: Cosponsored - To declare certain state judicial proceedings re Custody of Children (Box Box 78)
    - HR 11331: Sponsored - 3/7/78 Social Security Financing (Box Box 78)